it seems like the blood is on the tires
the monster that gave me life
flows in my veins
chun he
are you okay
yes everything is fine
just a little nauseous
I'll be with Macaw for a few days, sorry
that I can't be there
sorry
I'll be in the car okay
I'm sorry for the trouble
but where are you going for the funeral
she has a valid driver's license correct
yes there is
where is my compensation
sir
you must be very upset
but why don't you come and let me go
you killed a perfectly healthy boy
where is my compensation
who will compensate me for his death
sir we don't have to compensate
sir, let me go
we don't have to compensate
but
how did you know the deceased
well we
I'm his older brother
God what a terrible tragedy
he said it was his happiest moment
this was the place
It's really beautiful here
he drew it well
Minjirat drew
yes he drew you and her together unusually true
I'm her own son and I don't even want to look at her
and he doesn’t have a drop of blood with her
missed her so much
who cares about blood
I don't know what about the blood
but what matters is what they were to each other
I don't know
since childhood
I was always on the run from the past
and your mother
I was always afraid
that they will find me
I thought I would live like this all my life
it seems in the end
I'm tired of this
first I joined
to this investigation team
because mom asked
but I think part of me
I wanted to check
can I
this time I really wanted
stand your ground and fight back
but in the end
looks like
I ran away again
what did you run away from
conducting an investigation is a bit similar
to take care of the child
the more you think about it
the worse it gets
what does this all mean
I left with the investigation
nothing has changed
you're still the one
who did I choose
after long and careful observation
you didn't run away
just look at this beautiful view
you're in an even better place
I'm sorry
forgive me
everything's ok
hey buddy come here
run run let's go
Arabaidi doesn't like dogs
she's only pretending for us
caught you
hey guys
isn't he cute
look how he runs after me
macaw
wake up we're here changyeon
you can’t kindly wipe her mouth
I didn't drool
you are terrible
I'm on my way home, be careful, come out okay
see you at the top okay
Hello why is it so difficult to reach you?
you were right we have the doctor's address
which you were looking for
it seems kan and he knew about each other
the criminal will be caught soon no
A doctor's computer files were stolen from his home
Looks like the criminal was in a hurry this time
no mirrors or usual marks
the place was a complete mess
go back to the office now
black tire will not cooperate
if you're not there
guys, I can't help you now
the criminal will call soon
then you need to get a clue
Song Hyun Ho died because of me
minjae too
no wonder
that the team doesn't want my presence
I'm sorry
Mr. Sooyeol
problem with team members
Jeon and Shin will decide
that you come back to the office immediately
if you want to catch a criminal
you have to go yeah
well
come with me everything will be fine
Suyul you called the investigation a child
you can't take care of a child
only when you want
go
the criminal is on edge now
she's trying to cover her tracks
Captain Chas Yulia has been removed from this case
if you don't cooperate
you can go back to jail
I'll do so
keep an eye on this
why your son
after more than 20 years without contact
why now
can you leave us for a moment
we'll be fine
the child was small and also disabled
mother's victory was guaranteed
how do you know this
that guy from the administration
he chatted non-stop
why did you lose the custody battle
Hojoong it's okay
no need to answer any more questions
everything is fine don't worry hojoong
come on hojun come on
hujeong everything is fine
don't answer questions
everything is fine sorry son
he chose dad
the desire of such a small child will not affect the decision
you know that
dad
dad dad
it's okay dad I'm with you
before that he only knew how to cry and scream
and laugh when you're happy
he didn't say a word
but suddenly he said
dad out loud that was his 1st word
you insisted on this issue
knowing that it will be against you
you wanted the child to choose a father
you couldn't cope with him
but when did it become reality
you felt an insurmountable hatred for yourself
you became a mother
who abandoned her child
mistress black tire
my son captain chas uyol
became a policeman
to prove
that he's not like that at all
like me and that's why I took up this business
if he can't solve this case
he won't be able to forgive himself
so he tolerated his hated mother and refused to turn on
alarm he wanted to catch the criminal
but you only have a job
after you abandoned your child
if you can't even work
then you really are no one sure
you can't forgive yourself
I'm wrong what exactly are you trying to say
bring me suyolya
now he is also desperate
like you
look what the combined hopelessness will lead to
captain chas yol
good cop
he really deserves to be our captain
we refuse him not because
that he is your son
but because he hid it from us
because he didn't trust us
that's the thing
yes you're right
I was a coward
yes I refused it
I thought I couldn't handle it
if I couldn't be a good mother to Hojun
then I decided to at least succeed where I am needed
but you know what
at least
I didn't hug the baby with my arms
tainted by murder
if you had even a drop of motherly love
although there is no any responsibility
would you stop for the sake of the child
you cut off a man's tongue and tore off another's neck
what were you thinking about
when I returned home and saw my child
since I'm your mother
I won't kill you so what?
how eloquent you seem
upset
I'm just curious
you really help in this matter
for the sake of an hour I ate my son
what
yeah I just can't believe it
what if this is not a story about a mother helping her son?
what if it is the mother who is using her son for evil purposes?
that's what violent criminals do
if so
then I'll kill you
inspector kimnohi
hold on
police nambu
you overdid it with cilantro
the soup was too tasty
but too much cilantro
it was wrong to lie to us
why are you so sad
I thought you settled everything with the funeral at yesterday's funeral
not sure
I can't understand you either
thanks for reminding
that being 1 is the golden ticket
how about having a drink in the afternoon?
macaw
I can't drink anymore why
what happened
can you talk to me
pregnant
hey seriously wait
it's true
congratulations it's not him
this is good news, what’s wrong
just don't tell me
Sooyool doesn't want it now
now he can give him a full blast
but you need to knock his brains back into place
yes no he doesn't know yet
why didn't you tell him
that it's not him
I don’t know, I approached him myself and proposed
I will give birth to this child
whether he wants it or not
I have to show him
how nice it is to have 7
I'm jealous
his name is astrojian
This is a character invented by Serjanson
I'm not here for a warm welcome
but still at least until the end of the investigation
we need to work together
need to catch the criminal
there should be no new victims
thank you remember
what he told us
when I first arrived
it doesn’t matter if it’s drug control or
serious crimes
a real officer proves himself during investigations
now prove it
we will respond accordingly
blocked number
why are you with the police?
for the sake of my son
you know what I'm looking at now
corpse in the bathroom
this is a dump
you didn't kill that one
who deserved it
you did it
to save your skin
because he knew your real identity
now you understand
you and I are completely different
you kill people just because
what do you want to kill
there is no logic here
I know that you killed the cat
which you showed me
when I was a child
after being bullied by his father
you unleashed your rage on small and defenseless animals
yeonjun that is you
if you have a baby
I'm sure you'll follow in your father's footsteps
and make your child suffer better be silent
until I tore out your tongue
Damn, what deadly sparks fly between them
listen to chanisheng
it would be better if you killed me after that
how you killed my father
you act so noble
like you're some kind of hero
but in reality you are just a pathetic animal
which I failed
you should be grateful to me hey
I was the one who stopped the pack
when he dug on you and your son
your son now lives happily only thanks to me
and this is all your gratitude
what else is this
ok I'll make you regret it
that she didn't kill me after my father
you're in prison and I'm free
wait a minute you'll see
watch me destroy everything
what is dear to you
she said that you were happy because of her
how did you meet chunyeon
I thought all detectives were usually scary
yes I'm really scary
I mean
that I can be quite tough at work
I hope to see that day
when will you be afraid of me
why
well sometimes it gets scary
when you understand
that you're falling in love
why are there so many people in the bathroom
that the matchmaker still went to the bathroom
and here it’s a completely different atmosphere
this is only 1 meeting
and you already have secrets
turn off the power
아
hey don't worry about anything okay
safe driving
best driving
전원이 꺼져 있습니다
전화가 꺼져 있습니다
음성사서함으로 연결합니다
there's no one here
no car either
they must have gone somewhere
she's familiar to you
Any idea where it might be?
hey you call it driving
the car just passed the toll road
her son her son
where are they going
and Lijunyon's phone is still turned off
patrol cars
the traffic service has already been notified
Now almost all patrol cars are smart cars
I think they will find them
don't worry too much
parking
Well, now do you trust my driving?
can call the driver
no no I can handle it don't worry
I need to refuel okay
why is it turned off?
please select fuel type
Suyul's husband
if you are Sarah leave her immediately
Ms. Lee's phone turned on and she was next to Ishan Myung
send all available patrols to the area
ara killer minjae
tell me where are you
pass and chan myung and stay on route 92 yes sir
what happened
I just need to go to the toilet
to all district patrol officers, wait
Suyul it's me
listen to junyoung
I'll explain the details later
if you're a litter
you need to leave as soon as possible
faster and find other people
don't panic I'm on my way
can you tell where you are
myeongchon gas station
self service jeongyeon
don't hang up, keep your phone with you
understandable
ok don't be afraid
stay calm
go where there are a lot of people
never turn off your phone ok jeongyeon
하
아
our ochen can be so cute sometimes
Gesyn logistics
아아
아
Is anyone here?
suyeol I was able to escape
well done junyoung
are you okay what's going on
ara is really guilty
looks like it don't worry
the police are on their way, so am I
can you tell exactly where you are
I
kisyn logistics
but there's no one else here
the police are on their way
I'm going there too don't worry
take a deep breath
times
soo yul it seems
there's someone here
Mrs. Lichenyon
you are here Ms. Lichenyon this is the police
I'm here
we found Mrs. Li
there you go, hello sir
thank you very much
take her to a safe place first
we'll be there soon
yes sir
you can sit here
we will take you to a safe place
let's go to the station
why not him
let's go click
yes sir
how can you hear
what's going on there
how can you hear junyoung
arara please
don't do this I'm pregnant
hi nice to meet you
I'm Kang Yoon Joon
the gun is missing sir
hello
hello suyul it's you
ha
chun he sleeps great
the only thing that awaits her
when she wakes up
this is hell I hope
at least she'll have a nice dream
just try to touch her
and you will answer for it
Soo Yeol she was just a toy
thrown at you from the very beginning
Who are you to threaten me oh yeah exactly
I left you a little gift there
check the glove compartment
surprise
nambu police
I found the suspect's car
she goes to
Suel seems
The criminal is heading to Unsan
she doesn't hide it
Kang Yeongjun's old house in Dangwan and my old house too
send groups to all places
associated with the suspect
also the yonpo bridge needs to be closed
sir
and the Kyonpo Bridge was blocked
no one has crossed it for a long time
I think they are somewhere in this city
contacted the mining company
the vanguard forces of the cathedral have already gathered in the public center
we need to go there
oh I woke up, how are you?
cozy
this is my favorite place
I wonder if you'll like it
ara it's me chunion
yes of course
I know you chunyon
you are Chasu Yuli's wife and Jeong and Shin's daughter-in-law
I was the one who introduced you to him
to be honest
I tried to introduce him to other girls before you
but for some reason he was only interested in you
I knew the code to your door
and I received information from you every day from July
I even saw him every day
I didn't even need cameras or surveillance
all thanks to you
why are you doing this
she took care of me
it would be right to help her son wouldn't it
and she
hey
incredible to you true
need to come to my senses
you can meet your mother in law
it's too early to go crazy
eastern mine
sir yes thank you
wait a minute
yes sir
answer
hi shut up
listen to me you
you're probably wondering
where can I say
this is my hideout
there are a lot of bugs here and it's quite damp
but I like it
this is the basement
every time my father got drunk and made a scene
I was hiding here
tadam
I played doctor on this table
I was pretending
what's a paper knife?
scalpel and cut stray cats and dogs with it, one after another
you were right
the cat I showed you then
was also killed by me
I was just excited
when I acted against my father
you know what I mean
at some point the father became unimportant
I just wanted to continue
I started with very little
and then moved on to more
from animals to people
damn seriously
I should have killed my father myself
I really regret this
I always wanted to hide the pregnant creature
I thought the captain
if you put your mother to sleep
then the child will be under anesthesia
yes, you're interested too
yes
I searched the whole city looking for one like this
but I never found a single pregnant creature
maybe the city was too small
I cut everything else
but not that
I think today I can cross this off the list.
Are you still a child?
you took your anger out on your father
on defenseless animals
because you were weak then
but now that's not the case
if you're mad at me
take it out on me
you want me yes
and not the toy that I found
hey chun he
your mother in law just called you a toy
I asked you to be silent
our chunyeon
will remain alive thanks to her mother-in-law
I'll let her go but in exchange
come here yourself
the exchange will take place in 5 hours at the community center and after
I'll tell you when you come
if I suspect anything about the police
then I'll just kill chunyeon
see you later mom
in 5 hours it will be 11 am
jung and shin will come here
하하
open your mouth stop
make yourself look caring
untie me now it seems
our chun he is not ready to become a mother yet
ok forget about yourself
everything will be fine with your child
gone crazy
hey, I specifically helped you, creature
why did you spit in my face
look what you've done now
I'm all dirty
inspector chasu yul speaker
you will die if you go there
you know that
just deal with it
you give 1 to get two back
quite a good deal
last time you told me
that I should help the investigation
if I want to atone for my sins
it's pretty funny
I'm a prisoner
sentenced to death
even when I killed the scum
who deserved to die
I was put on trial
however when it comes to you
I have to do this
I understand
but I can't make that decision
after the closure of the mines they said
that the casino will be closed here
but it seems
things didn't work out
even former miners say
that there is no one
who knows all the nooks and crannies of the mines damn
so what now
after all the labor involved
we just have to sit back
told not to provoke the criminal
we just do it
what did you say, what about the captain?
his mother is his wife
and now also a child
I would have gone crazy by now
you're just incredibly naive
what does this mean
hell don't care
anyway
if we completely trust the words of Kan
and something will go wrong
we can release both kan and chen
both bloodthirsty killers set free
and if they are together
to be honest
I don't trust the captain either
after everything we've been through
that's what you think about captain cha
as far as I saw
he tried harder than anyone to catch this criminal
he suffered the most
when a new victim appeared
yeah it even got a little excessive
now I understand everything
jeon yi shin said
that captain cha became police
took up this matter
to prove
that he's not like that
like his mother to prove
as she is
to prove
that he is the one who saves lives
and he doesn’t take them away
who saves lives
prevents crimes for sure
that the number of victims almost drove him crazy
he probably thought
that he couldn't stop the murder
and even worse, the killer imitated his mother
almost
forced to relive mother's traumatic past
it must have been
so painful for him
and you still assume
that he would use his pregnant wife
to help kan and jeong
no I meant
Captain Chani is involved the other way around
these two are using it
but what if black tire had such intentions
As if serial killings weren't enough
what if she used her son
to escape
his life will be
so we must come together for his sake
let's see what happens next
hostage exchange
bosses never do this
will not agree
you said it yourself
the commissioner would never take such a risk
in which two serial killers may remain free
Chief Choe
jungho are you crazy
how can we trust jeong and shin so much
to let her go
we will put a tracker on her and catch her along with the criminal
this is our chance to catch the criminal too
Jeong and Shin agreed to cooperate
and if they are together
what if they are accomplices
what if this is not a chance to catch the criminals
and for the praying mantis an opportunity to escape
just in case
we will strengthen the perimeter of the exchange place
we will take all measures
to prevent escape
we don't have time
if the police find out about the pregnant hostage and kill her
How do you deal with the consequences?
we have a little more
than 4 hours we need to take her to the tire place right now
We shouldn't have gotten that woman involved in the first place.
jung hos you are enough
I take command
I refuse
what did you say
I'll finish the job myself
We received a report of a child crying
can I look around
Are you going to pick him up and raise him yourself?
sir there is no need for that
you know about juna canyon that day
if I had gone there then
I would have discovered kana
and if I had then taken the necessary measures
his father wouldn't have been killed either
then Kan would never have witnessed it
how jung yi shin killed his father
and after 23 years
we could avoid
that kan followed chon's actions and killed these people
what's wrong with you, you know
what was this village like
1/2 did not want the mines to close
the other 1/2 demanded it and wanted to build a casino
every day everyone got drunk and beat each other up
it was a complete mess
open on the street
even near our site
they fought, they beat each other until they bled
the fact that he beat the child at home
this is an excuse
it's just an excuse
in the end we did not fulfill our duty
what we couldn't do then
now
I want to do it myself
that Canyon June did it all
to save jeon and shin
Jung Yi Shin remains a dark chapter in police history
they wouldn't care
if she just disappeared
yes I understand
we'll take it
as approval and we will act accordingly
it's getting weird outside
who there was a special order from the commissioner
we continue to work independently
you tried to save me once
thank you
but can you tell me
how do you feel
when you try
save a person
ok let's move out
even when I killed those
who deserved to die
I was tried according to the law
I have to do this
mama bird walks through elementary school he san
investigation headquarters
series of dysfunctionality
you can go out
we'll stay here ready
When will the hostage exchange begin?
let's take positions here
here and here
to chase Kang and Jeong
and what kind of special order of the commissioner
it is not necessary to take the kana alive
close the case today at any cost
except for the treated hour of pleasure
do not use extreme measures for the safety of hostages
for security reasons
or tea to stop kana
Jeon and Shin can be eliminated
here is his order
communication via channel 8
as soon as the neon is returned
let's start the pursuit right away
show your hand
kana has a gun
so you should wear this
many people want me dead
Kan is not the only one
I'm not
so show me your hand
I'll be there
don't worry
go straight up the mountain behind shaft number 2 and follow
so that the praying mantis is in handcuffs
and you were unarmed
if someone tries to deceive
or something suspicious will start
chun he and your child will be killed immediately
are you ready
the chick brought the mother bird out of the center of the community moving forward
the praying mantis is really here
r are you coming
1 walk around the foot of the mountain in a wide circle
and explore buildings or caves
which can serve as shelter
be alert don't forget
the criminal has a gun
as soon as the exchange takes place
our troops will enter
shoot as soon as he is safe
I was so disappointed
this is your only chance
if you want to kill me
tell me where the tire went
unofficial orientation announced for you two
why were you so lenient towards her
and this creature burned my mother alive
Isn't the life of a monster lonely?